Guide to the Linda Cobb Conaway Duke University Ephemera Collection, 1963-1969, undated UA.30.01.0080
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Linda Cobb Conaway Duke University Ephemera collection
1963-1969, undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. University Archives
Conaway, Linda Cobb
UA.30.01.0080
0.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains ephemera such as brochures, programs, flyers, and playbills collected by Linda Cobb Conaway while she was a student at the Woman's College. The subjects of the ephemera include performances by Hoof' N' Horn and speakers brought in by Duke University Union's Major Speakers Committee, as well as other student events. The collection ranges in date from 1963 to 1969, and undated.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Biographical Note
Linda Cobb Conaway graduated from the Woman's College at Duke in 1969.
Collection Overview
Collection contains ephemera such as brochures, programs, flyers, and playbills collected by Linda Cobb Conaway while she was a student at the Woman's College. The subjects of the ephemera include performances by Hoof' N' Horn and speakers brought in by Duke University Union's Major Speakers Committee, as well as other student events. The collection ranges in date from 1963 to 1969, and undated.
Duke University. Hoof 'n' Horn; Duke University. University Archives; Duke University. Union; Conaway, Linda Cobb; Duke University--Students--Social life and customs
- Duke University Ephemera
  - Playbill - Marcel Marceau, 1965 Oct. 28 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Royal Winnipeg Ballet, 1965 Nov. 5 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - John Alexander, 1966 Jan. 14 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1966 Mar. 7 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Student Union the Odd Couple, 1966 Oct. 10 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Duke Festival of Contemporary Arts Dance, 1966 Oct. 14-15 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Julian Bream, 1966 Nov. 15 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Porgy and Bess, 1967 Jan. 11 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Tomas Vasary, 1967 Feb. 3 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Tamas Vasary, 1967 Feb. 3 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Duke Festival of the Contemporary Arts Music, 1967 Feb. 8-11 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1967 Mar. 17 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Robert Shaw Chorale and Orchestra, 1967 Apr. 11 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - The Czech Philharmonic, 1967 Oct. 20 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1967 Nov. 2 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - The Play of Daniel, 1967 Nov. 29 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - The Play of Daniel, 1967 Nov. 29 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Daniel Barenboim, 1968 Feb. 7 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - The Fantasticks, 1968 Feb. 9 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - The Royal Winniped Ballet, 1968 Feb. 20 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Stop the World I Want to Get Off, 1968 Feb. 22 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - The Branko Krsmanovich Chorus, 1968 Apr. 3 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Sweet Charity, 1968 Apr. 26-27 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Major Attractions Committee Simon and Garfunkel, 1968 Oct. 12 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Simon and Garfunkel, 1968 Oct. 12 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Hoof' N' Horn, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - You, Me and the World, 1969 Feb. 5 (Box 1)
  - Playbill - Shirley Verrett, 1969 Apr. 11 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Major Speaker's Series Martin Agronsky, 1965 Oct. 29 (Box 1)
  - Brochure - Major Speakers Series, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Program - Major Speakers Committee Wayne Morse, 1966 Nov. 14 (Box 1)
  - Poster - Wayne Morse on United States Foreign Policy, 1966 Nov. 14 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Major Speakers Series Byron White, 1967 Mar. 6 (Box 1)
  - Program - Major Speakers Committee Christopher C. Kraft, Jr., 1967 May 9 (Box 1)
  - Brochure - Major Speakers Committee Norman Cousins, 1967 Oct. 12 (Box 1)
  - Program - Major Speakers Committee Symposium on Foreign Policy, 1967 Nov. 28 (Box 1)
  - Program - Major Speakers Committee Gerald R. Ford, 1968 Feb. 2 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Major Speakers Committee Adam Yarmolinsky, 1968 Feb. 23 (Box 1)
  - Program - Major Speakers Committee Adam Clayton Powell, 1968 Apr. 1 (Box 1)
  - Brochure - James A. Thomas Memorial Room Woman's College Library, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Program - A Question of Values Symposium, 1965 Nov. 14-16 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Artur Rubinstein, 1966 Feb. 15 (Box 1)
  - Program - The Philadelphia Orchestra, 1966 Nov. 25-26 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - The Look Away, [circa 1967] (Box 1)
  - Brochure - Adventure Series, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1967 Mar. 21 (Box 1)
  - Program - Impact: The Postwar Generation Symposium, 1967 Nov. 5-7 (Box 1)
  - Brochure - Duke Folk Festival, 1968 Mar. 15-16 (Box 1)
  - Exhibition Catalogue - Philip Jamison, 1969 Mar. 2-22 (Box 1)
  - Invitation - Exhibition Event, 1969 Mar. 9 (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Education Affairs Committee Vladimir Dedijer, undated (Box 1)
  - Flyer - Education Affairs Committee GeorgeMcGovern, undated (Box 1)